// TASK:    This is another difficult one. Possibly the most difficult. So think
//          CAREFULLY about the process. This process releases a Process p's
//          MemoryArea from Memory m.
//
//          First, find the index at which the process resides by matching the
//          procNum from the Memory's MemoryArea to the procNum of the incoming
//          Process p. Next, find the end location of the Memory area. You do
//          this by looking at the NEXT MemoryArea's end. If it is -1, the
//          current MemoryArea is your end index. I used a single for loop and
//          iterated over m using m.size as a length. When I found the process,
//          I saved i as the start location and when I found the -1, I saved the
//          i as the end location and then set i to the size of m to exit the loop.
//
//          Now that you have a the start index and the end index, you need to
//          roll processes forward into the vacant slot. When you get to the end,
//          you need to open the rest of the space back up for other processes.
//          Doing this takes some deeper thought. So... first, we want to loop from
//          the start location to the end location using a for loop. Inside the
//          loop we're looking for two cases: 1) are we at the end location
//          where we need to consolidate or 2) are we not. If we aren't at the
//          end, we shift the process forward. If we are at the end, we reset
//           the end blocks.
//
//          Let's start with case 2 as it's the easier of the two: we are not at
//          the end. If we aren't at the end we need to: set the current MemoryArea
//          end to the current MemoryArea's start plus the NEXT MemoryArea's end
//          minus the NEXT MemoryArea's start. This gives us a new end for the
//          current MemoryArea. Next, we set the current MemoryArea's proc to
//          the NEXT MemoryArea's proc. Finally, we adjust the NEXT MemoryArea's 
//          start to our current MemoryArea's end plus one.
//
//          When we get to i == end_location - 1, we have to do something
//          different... I actually created a helper function for this, but you
//          can just put it right within the decision structure. First, we set
//          our current start to the PREVIOUS MemoryArea's end plus 1. Next, we
//          set our current end to m.size. We then set the current proc's
//          procNum and time to zero. Finally we deinitialize the memory by
//          setting the NEXT MemoryArea's start and end to -1.
//
//          Read this description... a TON and understand what you are trying to do.
//